clickastro.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy - Privacy and Terms - Clickastro.com

Privacy Policy

1\. What are the information we collect from you?

Astro-Vision Futuretech Pvt. Ltd. offers highly personalized content and services to all its customers. So, when you use or access any of our products/services, we may collect some information about you which are described below. 

Use Of IP Address

When you fill the details for availing our services, we track your IP address to find the users location, device type, and also to find if there any problems with our software/services and to help us remember you and your preferences when you revisit our website. An Internet protocol (I.P.) address is a set of numbers that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you log on to your internet service provider or through your company's local area network (LAN) or wide area network (WAN). Web servers, the powerful computers that provide web pages for viewing, automatically identify your computer by the IP address assigned to it during your session online. We may collect I.P. addresses for some purposes (for example, to report anonymous user information to our advertisers and to audit the use of our site). We do not ordinarily link a user's I.P. address to a person's personal information, which means we will have a record of each user's session but the user remains anonymous to us. We will use I.P. addresses to identify users of our site when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site's terms of use or to protect our service, site, or other users. 

Use of Cookies and Server Logs

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for the record–keeping purposes. We occasionally use cookies on the Website. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Website. We set a persistent cookie to store your toolbar or app name and/or username so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on the Website. If you reject cookies, you will still be able to use the Website, but your ability to use some areas of the Website may be limited. Some of our business partners may use cookies on the Website. Such cookies may be used to analyze the Website traffic in the Website and monitor operational performance of the Website. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Astro-Vision Futuretech Pvt. Ltd. only and does not cover the use of cookies by any other third party. Server logs capture certain non–Personally Identifying data, such as the time and date of a web visit, the browser and operating system being used, the IP address or domain name of the user's ISP, and the web URL a user linked from. This information is generally used to help us plan system enhancements when necessary and to provide content which is compatible with our visitors' web browsing systems. We do not use server logs in any way that may disclose your PII.

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site. We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website. You may put astrology as a service, include all these and offer the whole as a package for sale.

Clear Gifs/Web Beacons

The products and services we use to measure and optimize the traffic including visitor feedback and analytic tools may employ a technology called Clear Gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs). The technology is used to better manage content on the Website by informing us if the content is optimized to meet the needs of the Website visitors. Clear Gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to measure the online movements of Website users in different pages on the Website. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, Clear Gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Astro-Vision Futuretech Pvt. Ltd. does not access PII of Website visitors via the Clear Gifs. The Clear Gifs are solely used for the purposes described in this paragraph.

Other Information

Any other pieces of information collected are truly based on our communication with our clients and are used only for addressing their specific needs. We give our customers the personalized services and nothing that is irrelevant to their query. We make sure that the e-mail address given will be safe with us and will never disclose it to the third parties.

2\. What do we do with the information collected?

Our purpose in collecting information about you is to provide you with products, services and information of your interests and preferences. We use the information for, 

• confirm your identity  
• administer your account on any of our websites  
• to enforce our terms, conditions and policies  
• provide personalized services and offers for you based upon your interests;  
• respond to inquiries if you have any queries regarding our services  
• enable you to search for information on our websites.  
• contact you regarding customer service and customer surveys;  
• track your behaviour on our website, to enhance our services and better user experience.  
• inform you about the changes we made to our services/policies/website.  
• understand general customer trends and patterns to improve existing and ongoing marketing strategies for our products and services  
• inform you about our new products, services, promotions, offers etc  

3\. Do we keep your information safe? What are the Security and Payment Information?

Your privacy is much important to us. All the information collected were safe and secure. We do not disclose it to any third parties. Also, we do not collect any payment information. All the payment information are handled in a secured manner by third-party payment gateways. In that case, also, we do not permit our third-party sites to use your information to market their own products or services to you directly. However, please keep in mind that, no technology is completely safe and secure. So, we cannot fully eliminate the risks. But we have implemented the industry standard technical and procedural measures to keep all your information safe. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. 

4\. How long do we maintain your personal data?

We will retain all the personal data only as long as necessary as we have an obligation to our client to provide the services offered. Also, we hold the information for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. Any PII (personally identifiable information) that we collect is stored and processed on servers located in the U.S or India. For persons in European Union countries, as used herein, terms such as "personally identifiable information" refer to "personal data" as defined by EU Directive 95/46/EC. By using the Website or its services, you expressly agree that we may transfer your PII outside the European Union in connection with the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy. You understand that regardless of jurisdiction, use of PII will continue to be governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

5\. To whom do we disclose information collected about you and do we share the information with third parties?

We may share your user data with other service providers, partners etc., in the event of a business transaction or for law enforcement purposes, as set out below: 

• **Service Providers**

We share your information with third party service providers mainly for processing payments on our behalf; helping us to maintain our databases etc. But we do not allow our third-party sites to use your information to market their own products or services to you directly.

• **Required by Law**

If required by law or asks by any of the government entities we may disclose all the information collected as permitted by the law.

• **Enforce Legal Rights**

We may disclose information about you to the government or to the law under certain circumstances. We reserve the right to release that personal information collected through the website to government officials if necessary.

• **Our Advisors**

We may also share information collected about you with our auditors, legal advisors subjected to standard confidentiality obligations

6\. What are the policies of linked websites?

Our website may contain links to other sites that are not covered under this Privacy Policy. Our vision in providing a link to other websites is entirely for better user experience and for your convenience. It does not signify that we are responsible or we guarantee any such other website or location or its contents. When you click such links and enter another website, they may or may not collect information from you. But, we have no control over and we are not responsible for the practices or the content of such websites. Also, please keep in mind that the privacy policy of these websites are different from ours and our privacy policy is not applicable to them. 

7\. What are the terms regarding any future changes to this privacy policy?

We may update or change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on the feedback received from our clients or as a result of a change of policy of the organisation. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

8\. How can you contact us?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, or about the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at: 

Head Office

1st Floor,White Tower,

Kuthappadi Road,

Thammanam P O, Cochin - 682 032

Kerala, India.

Phone: +91 484 2343925, 3390000

Customer support:

Direct: +91 484 3390032

E-mail: predictions@clickastro.com

CIN: U72200KL2001PTC014651
